Guide to the Cornell University Department of Theatre Arts records, 1893-2008.
Cornell University Department of Theatre Arts records
- Series IV. Cornell University Theatre and Cornell Dramatic Club
  - Programs, Posters and other Printed Materials
    - Sponsored Performances
      - The Serpent; Ubu Cocu, March 14-15, 1969; The Open Theatre (Box 44, Folder 75)
    - Sage Dramatic Club program, 1901 (Box 44, Folder 76)
    - Cornell Women's Dramatic Club programs, 1915-1925 (Box 44, Folder 77)
    - Kermis play programs, 1915-1919, 1925, 1936-1941 (Box 44, Folder 78)
    - Le Cercle Français programs, circa 1921-1925 (Box 44, Folder 79)
    - Annual New York State Community Dramatics Contest, 1929-1942 (Box 44, Folder 80)
    - Miscellaneous programs from other theater groups and clubs, 1907-1957 (Box 44, Folder 81)
    - Cornell University Theatre film publicity, circa 1938-1952 (Box 44, Folder 82)
    - Articles, press releases, newspaper clippings (Box 44, Folder 83)
    - Hamlet Festival flyer, Spring 1979 (Box 44, Folder 84)
    - Willard Straight Hall, pamphlet and flyers, 1925, 1950 (Box 44, Folder 85)
    - List of one-act play programs, 1940-1953 (Box 44, Folder 86)
    - List of New York State play programs, 1940-1942, undated (Box 44, Folder 87)
  - Photographs and Slides
    - Student photographs: E.L. McCollum, A.P. Howes, 1905-1906 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Group photograph, January 26, 1917 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - New York State Fair Country Theatre, 1919-1923 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Unidentified backstage photos (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Campus theatre [used from 1917 to 1925] (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Campus theatre [used 1924-1955?] (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - 4 people standing beside dress on mannequin, Performing Arts Center, circa 1983 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Theatre productions and international travels, photos and slides from May Newfeld, 1960s (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Barbara Wallace (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Franchot Tone (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Cornell Dramatic Club officers, 1951-1952 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Taming of the Shrew, 1951 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - The Lyceum, Ithaca, NY (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Ibsen's "An Enemy of the People," Lyceum Theatre, March 5, 1909 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Gogol's Inspector General (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Unidentified production at the Lyceum (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - CDC tour to Latin America, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Sidney Kingsley's Wonderdark Epilogue, 1928 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - You Touched Me!, October 1948 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - CDC 50th anniversary event, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - CDC 50th anniversary luncheon, March 7, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - CDC 50th anniversary banquet, June 12, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Rural dramatic competitions, circa 1933 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Traffic Signals, directed by Alexander Drummond, 1926, 1927, 1936 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - An Enemy of the People, circa 1934? (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Men playing cards; unidentified older man (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Roberts Hall theater (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Alexander Drummond (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Arms and the Man, backstage (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Arsenic and Old Lace (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Blithe Hour (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Deep are the Roots (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Ladies in Retirement (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Two Blind Mice (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Summer and Smoke (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Arms and the Man (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Trial by Jury (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Dr. Knock (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Princess Ida (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Boy Meets Girl (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Thunder Rock (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Treasure Island (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - CDC images from magazine (including one with Sidney Kingsley, Franchot Tone, and Dan Duryea), undated (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Unidentified group photographs (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - "I Would Found an Institution" photographs, April 26-27, 1935 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Unidentified cast and play photos, undated (before 1950) (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Setting for "Seven Keys to Baldpate," produced by the Benton Harbor Teacher's Club, November 18-19, 1926 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Unidentified color photograph (possibly Pirates of Penzance), undated (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Thor, with Angels, December 11-12, 1954 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - The Skin of Our Teeth, October 27-30, 1955 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Misalliance, October 25-28, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - The Haunted House, May 1958 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - The Taming of the Shrew, May 14-17, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - The Jew of Malta, November 12-15, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - The Knack, July 21-23, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Death of a Salesman, January 14-17, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Night Must Fall, 1948 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - A Different Drummer, April 17-20, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Three Way Split (The Sandbox; The Room; The Future Is in Eggs), April 12-15, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - A Midsummer Night's Dream, April 22-23, 29-30, 1927 (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - "Pyramus and Thisbe" from A Midsummer Night's Dream. Directed by P.B. Pettit, undated (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - The Little Clay Cart, circa 1927 (Box 24, Folder 37)
    - Volpone, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 38)
    - Photographs taken during 1965-1966 school year by Louise Manning, Photograph album (Box 35)
    - Summer Theatre personnel, 1964 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Unidentified play directed by M. Carlson featuring Sue Nohr, Al Gingold, and Beth Neustadt, March 1971 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Drama Club, 1941-1942 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Cornell University Touring Company-How to Grow a Musical (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - "The Rogues' Comedy," Lyceum Theatre, April 26, 1912 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - The Contrast, 1925 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - The Contrast, 1925; 5 photographs (Box 46)
    - Once Upon a Hill, 1950; 5 photographs (Box 46)
    - Taming of the Shrew, undated; 8 photographs (Box 46)
    - Unidentified photographs (3 plays, 1 backstage), undated; 4 photographs (Box 46)
    - Awake and Sing, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - The Mad Woman of Chaillot, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Desire Under the Elms, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - The Family Reunion, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Ten Nights in a Bar-Room, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - The School for Wives, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - The Tempest, 1953 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Mixin' Up the Rent, undated (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - "Taming of the Shrew", undated (Box 45)
    - Photographs taken backstage, undated; Ross Wagner '55; 6 photographs (Box 45)
    - The Lady's Not for Burning, 1953-1954; [character studies] (Box 45)
    - The Inspector General, 1953-1955; [character studies] (Box 45)
    - The Pursuit of Happiness, 1954-1955 (Box 47)
    - Thor, with Angels, 1954-1955 (Box 48)
    - Dark of the Moon, 1954-1955; 2 photographs (Box 48)
    - Dark of the Moon, 1954-1955 (Mapcase-folder 3)
    - Charley's Aunt, 1954-1955 (Box 48)
    - Blood Wedding, 1954-1955 (Box 48)
    - Twelfth Night, 1954-1955 (Box 48)
    - The Would-Be Invalid, 1955-1956; [character studies] (Box 45)
    - The Would-Be Invalid, 1955-1956 (Box 47)
    - Amahl and the Night Visitors, 1955-1956 (Box 47)
    - Electra by Sophocles, 1955-1956 (Box 48)
    - The Skin of our Teeth, 1955-1956 (Box 48)
    - Right You Are, 1956; 4 photographs (Box 47)
    - Right You Are, 1956 (Mapcase-folder 3)
    - The Flowering Peach, 1955-1956 (Box 48)
    - The Tavern, 1958 (Box 48)
    - Under Milkwood, 1959 (Box 46)
    - Medea, 1961 (Box 45)
    - Une Esquisse de la Comédie Musicale Américaine, 1962 (Mapcase-folder 2)
    - Une Esquisse de la Comédie Musicale Américaine, 1962 (Mapcase-folder 4)
    - The Rivals, undated (Box 45)
    - The Lake Guns of Seneca and Cayuga, undated (Mapcase-folder 4)
    - The Good Woman of Setzuan, undated (Box 47)
    - How to Grow a Musical, undated (Box 47)
    - Rashomon, undated (Box 47)
    - The Fantasticks, undated (Box 47)
    - Hedda Gabler, undated (Box 47)
    - Papa is All, undated (Box 47)
    - All Summer Long, undated (Box 48)
    - The Witchfinders, undated (Box 48)
    - The Country Wife, undated (Box 48)
    - Misalliance, undated (Box 48)
    - Man and Superman, undated (Box 48)
    - Iolanthe, undated (Box 48)
    - A Different Drummer, undated (Box 48)
    - Theater at Cornell in the 1930s, Glass slides (Box 50)
    - Country Theater, Berkeley High School, (Cornell?) theater productions, set construction, Glass slides and glass negatives (Box 50)
    - Lists of slides for P.S. 48, circa 1941-1942 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Yale-Rockefeller Theatre Collection Catalogue notes and slide ordering correspondence, circa 1939 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - An American Festival materials, 1982, 1989 (Box 54)
    - From the Ground Up: Grassroots Theatre in Historical and Contemporary Perspective, 1993 (Box 54)
    - A Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum, Expression (Box 56, Folder 1)
      Richard Shank, director
    - Aaron Slick from Punkin Crick, 1936-1937 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Accent on Youth, 1940 (Box 56, Folder 3)
      Includes program
    - The Acharnians, 1968-1969 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Acid Drops, 1926-03-05-1926-03-06 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Across the Board on Tomorrow Morning, 1943 (Box 56, Folder 73)
    - Across the Continent, 1942-01-09-1942-01-17 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Action!, 1927-10 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - The Adding Machine, 1932 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - The Adoration of the Magi, 1926-12-11-1926-12-15 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - The Admirable Bashville, 1928-03-02-1928-03-10 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - The Affairs of Anatole, 1944 (Box 56, Folder 74)
    - An Affair of Honor, 1933-1934 (Box 56, Folder 10)
      Peter Stelzer, director
    - After the Fall, 1976 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Ah, Wilderness!, 1947-05 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Ah, Wilderness!, 1965 (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - The Albany Depot, Undated (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Alice in Wonderland, 1922 (Box 56, Folder 15)
      Freshman women
    - Alice in Wonderland, 1928 (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - Alice in Wonderland, 1931 (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - Alice in Wonderland, 1933-1934 (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - Alice in Wonderland, 1937 (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - Alison's House, 1947-12 (Box 56, Folder 20)
    - All Summer Long, 1956-11 (Box 56, Folder 21)
    - Amahl and the Night Visitors, 1955-1957 (Box 56, Folder 22)
    - America Passes By, 1920 (Box 56, Folder 23)
    - American Dream; Zoo Story, 1976 (Box 56, Folder 24)
    - Among the Breakers, Undated (Box 56, Folder 25)
    - Anatol, 1944 (Box 56, Folder 26)
    - And May God Have Mercy, 1938 (Box 56, Folder 27)
      Includes scene sketches
    - And the Pursuit of Happiness, 1939 (Box 56, Folder 28)
    - Andorra, 1967-11 (Box 56, Folder 29)
    - Androcles and the Lion, 1922 (Box 56, Folder 30)
    - Angel Street, 1950-08-1950-10 (Box 56, Folder 31)
    - Another Language, 1933-1934 (Box 56, Folder 32)
    - Antigone, 1959 (Box 56, Folder 33)
    - Antigone, 1969-1970 (Box 56, Folder 34)
    - Antique Shop, Undated (Box 56, Folder 35)
    - Antony and Cleopatra, 1974-1975 (Box 56, Folder 36)
    - Apartment 3-D, 1939 (Box 56, Folder 37)
    - The Appel Tree, 1969-1970 (Box 56, Folder 38)
    - Aria da Capo, 1949-11 (Box 56, Folder 39)
    - Arms and the Man, 1924 (Box 56, Folder 40)
    - Arms and the Man, 1950 (Box 56, Folder 41)
    - Arms and the Man, 1975 (Box 56, Folder 42)
    - Around the Corner, 1928 (Box 56, Folder 43)
    - Around the Corner, 1938 (Box 56, Folder 44)
    - Art and Appreciation, 1937-1938 (Box 56, Folder 45)
    - As You Like It, 1950 (Box 56, Folder 46)
    - As You Like It, 1963-03 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - The Ascent of F6, 1949 (Box 56, Folder 47)
    - The Aulis Difficulty, 1925-12 (Box 56, Folder 48)
    - The Autumn Garden, 1953 (Box 56, Folder 49)
    - Awake and Sing, 1952 (Box 56, Folder 50)
    - Awake and Sing, 1971-1972 (Box 56, Folder 51)
    - Bald Soprano, 1966 (Box 56, Folder 52)
    - The Bank Account, 1919-05 (Box 56, Folder 53)
    - The Barretts of Wimpole Street, 1948-10-30 (Box 56, Folder 54)
    - Barthol'mew Fair, 1967-11 (Box 56, Folder 55)
    - The Bat, 1932 (Box 56, Folder 56)
    - Beautiful People, 1948 (Box 56, Folder 57)
    - Beauty and the Beast, 1949-12 (Box 56, Folder 58)
    - Beauty and the Jacobin, Undated (Box 56, Folder 59)
    - Before Breakfast, Undated (Box 56, Folder 60)
    - Behind the Beyond, 1920 (Box 56, Folder 61)
    - Behind the Beyond, 1927 (Box 56, Folder 62)
    - Bell, Book, and Candle, 1958 (Box 56, Folder 63)
    - Berkeley Square, 1932 (Box 56, Folder 64)
    - Bernardine, 1956-12 (Box 56, Folder 65)
    - Between the Soup and the Savoury, 1918-1927 (Box 56, Folder 66)
    - The Bewitched, 1977-1976 (Box 56, Folder 67)
    - Beyond the Horizon, 1943 (Box 56, Folder 68)
    - Bill Greenfield's Legend, 1941 (Box 56, Folder 69)
    - Bird in Hand, 1920-12 (Box 56, Folder 70)
    - The Birthday Party, 1976-1977 (Box 56, Folder 71)
    - Bishop's Candlesticks, 1939 (Box 56, Folder 72)
    - Blind, 1921-11 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Blithe Spirit, Undated (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Blood Knot, 1967-07 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Blood Wedding, 1955-04 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - The Glass Menagerie, 1949-10 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Happy Birthday, 1949-12 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Hay Fever, 1939-12 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Jim Dandy, 1942 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - John Gabriel Borkman, 1945 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Journey of the 5th Horse, 1968-1969 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Mary Stuart, 1968-02 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Monday, 1943 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - The Monkey's Paw, Undated (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Morn to Midnight, 1933 (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - A Month in the Country, 1977-1978 (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - Morning's at Seven, 1942 (Box 57, Folder 18)
    - Mourning Call, 1930-02 (Box 57, Folder 19)
    - The Mouse, 1928 (Box 57, Folder 20)
    - The Mousetrap, 1922 (Box 57, Folder 21)
    - The Mousetrap, 1926-10 (Box 57, Folder 22)
    - Murder is Fun, 1944-11 (Box 57, Folder 23)
    - Music Hall Review, 1929 (Box 57, Folder 24)
    - Music Hall Show, 1941 (Box 57, Folder 25)
      Includes Program
    - My Heart's in the Highland, 1941 (Box 57, Folder 26)
    - My Sister, My Sister, 1980-11 (Box 57, Folder 27)
    - My Three Angels, 1959 (Box 57, Folder 28)
    - Mysterious Murder of Maria Marten, 1977-1978 (Box 57, Folder 29)
    - Napoleon's Barber, 1925-12 (Box 57, Folder 30)
    - Narrow Road to the Deep North, 1969-1970 (Box 57, Folder 31)
    - Neighbors, 1928-02 (Box 57, Folder 32)
    - Never-the-less, 1924 (Box 57, Folder 33)
    - A Night at an Inn, 1926-10 (Box 57, Folder 34)
    - Night Must Fall, 1948-05 (Box 57, Folder 35)
    - Nine Girls, 1944 (Box 57, Folder 36)
    - No Mother to Guide Her, 1942-11 (Box 57, Folder 37)
    - No Place to Be Somebody, 1974-1975 (Box 57, Folder 38)
    - No Smoking, 1926-11 (Box 57, Folder 39)
    - Nothing Doing, 1939 (Box 57, Folder 40)
    - Number Tea, Undated (Box 57, Folder 41)
    - O'Flaherty, VC, 1928-03 (Box 57, Folder 42)
    - Oedipus, 1963-01 (Box 57, Folder 43)
    - Oedipus, 1973-1974 (Box 57, Folder 44)
    - Of Mice and Men, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 45)
    - The Offering of the Shepherds, 1926-12 (Box 57, Folder 46)
    - Oh Dad, Poor Dad..., 1970 (Box 57, Folder 47)
    - The Old Lady Shows Her Medals, 1922 (Box 57, Folder 48)
    - The Old Ladies, 1954-08 (Box 57, Folder 49)
    - Old Times, 1973-1974 (Box 57, Folder 50)
    - Olympia, 1933 (Box 57, Folder 51)
    - On Approval, Undated (Box 57, Folder 52)
    - On ne badine pas avec l'amour, 1928 (Box 57, Folder 53)
    - Once Upon a Hill, 1946-1956 (Box 57, Folder 54)
      Includes programs
    - One of Cleopatra's Knights, 1927-05 (Box 57, Folder 55)
    - One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest, 1960 (Box 57, Folder 56)
    - Op-'O-Me-Thumb, 1919-1926 (Box 57, Folder 57)
    - The Open Door, 1919 (Box 57, Folder 58)
    - Orontea, 1967-1968 (Box 57, Folder 59)
    - Othello, 1958-01 (Box 57, Folder 60)
    - Our God Brother Joseph, 1934 (Box 57, Folder 61)
    - Our Lean Years, 1937 (Box 57, Folder 62)
    - Our Town, 1944-1976 (Box 57, Folder 63)
    - Outward Bound, 1927-1928 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Outward Bound, 1945-1946 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Overruled, 1931 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Overruled, 1953 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Overtones, 1924 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Papa is All, 1957-06 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Paradiso! Paradiso!, 1954 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - The Parian, 1927-10 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Patience, 1953-03 (Box 58, Folder 9)
      Includes Programs
    - Paul Invents, 1951-03 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Pentesilea, 1980 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - The People, 1920 (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Philadelphia Story, 1948 (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Phipps, 1926 (Box 58, Folder 21)
    - The Physicists, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Pictures in the Hallway, 1961-01 (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - The Pied Piper of Hamelin, Undated (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - Pierrette, 1928 (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - The Pigeon, 1947 (Box 58, Folder 18)
    - Pinafore, 1951 (Box 58, Folder 19)
    - Pirates of Penzance, 1952-03 (Box 58, Folder 20)
    - Plain Folks, Undated (Box 58, Folder 22)
    - The Playboy of the Western World, 1925-01-1927-08 (Box 58, Folder 23)
    - The Playgoers, 1919-12 (Box 58, Folder 24)
    - The Play's the Thing, 1950-04 (Box 58, Folder 25)
    - Plots and Playwrights, 1931 (Box 58, Folder 26)
    - The Pot Boiler, 1921-1927 (Box 58, Folder 27)
    - The Pot Boiler, 1945 (Box 58, Folder 28)
    - A Pot of Broth, 1926 (Box 58, Folder 29)
    - A Pound on Demand, 1946 (Box 58, Folder 30)
    - The Power of Fate, Undated (Box 58, Folder 31)
    - Press Cuttings, 1914-05 (Box 58, Folder 32)
    - Princess Ida, Undated (Box 58, Folder 33)
    - Private Lives, 1960 (Box 58, Folder 34)
    - Priveleges and Privations, 1939-03 (Box 58, Folder 35)
    - Pleasure Gardens, 1932-05 (Box 58, Folder 36)
    - The Price, 1975 (Box 58, Folder 72)
    - A Proposal Under Difficulties, 1926-02 (Box 58, Folder 37)
    - Pullman Car Hiawatha, 1943-02 (Box 58, Folder 38)
    - Pursuit of Happiness, 1955-05 (Box 58, Folder 39)
    - Puss n Boots, 1975-1976 (Box 58, Folder 40)
    - Pyramus and Thisbe, 1953 (Box 58, Folder 41)
    - "Q", 1927 (Box 58, Folder 42)
    - The Queen's Husband, 1934-11 (Box 58, Folder 43)
    - A Question of Principle, 1926-03 (Box 58, Folder 44)
    - Quiet Facing the Park, 1944-1945 (Box 58, Folder 45)
    - The Quodwrangle, 1927-11 (Box 58, Folder 46)
    - Rain, 1925 (Box 58, Folder 47)
    - Rappings and Table Movings, 1942-05 (Box 58, Folder 48)
    - Rare Wine, Undated (Box 58, Folder 49)
    - Rashomon, 1962-12 (Box 58, Folder 50)
    - Rehearsal, 1924-1939 (Box 58, Folder 51)
    - Release, 1927-10 (Box 58, Folder 52)
    - The Rest Cure, Undated (Box 58, Folder 53)
    - Revue, 1928 (Box 58, Folder 54)
    - Ricardo and Viola, 1925-02 (Box 58, Folder 55)
    - Richard III, 1966-12 (Box 58, Folder 56)
    - Riders to the Sea, 1917-1919 (Box 58, Folder 57)
    - Right You Are If You Think You Are, 1926 (Box 58, Folder 58)
    - Right You Are If You Think You Are, 1955 (Box 58, Folder 59)
    - Right You Are If You Think You Are, 1975-1976 (Box 58, Folder 60)
    - The Rivals, 1937 (Box 58, Folder 61)
    - The Rivals, 1958-12 (Box 58, Folder 62)
    - Rocking Chairs, 1927-10 (Box 58, Folder 63)
    - Romantic Young Lady, 1939 (Box 58, Folder 64)
    - Romeo and Juliet, 1952-02 (Box 58, Folder 65)
    - Romeo and Juliet, 1964-03 (Box 58, Folder 66)
    - Romeo and Juliet, 1977-12 (Box 58, Folder 67)
    - The Room, 1961-1962 (Box 58, Folder 68)
    - Rosencrantz and Guildenster are Dead, 1971-1972 (Box 58, Folder 69)
    - Rosmersholm, 1964-01 (Box 58, Folder 70)
    - Rules of the Game, 1969-03 (Box 58, Folder 71)
    - R.U.R., 1928-01 (Box 58, Folder 73)
    - R.U.R., 1946-12 (Box 58, Folder 74)
    - Sabotage, 1917-1920 (Box 58, Folder 75)
    - Saint John, 1980 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Sam Average, 1920-05 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Sand Dancing, 1981 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Sandbox, 1961-1962 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Sappho's Lover, 1927 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Sauce for the Gosling, 1928-02 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - School for Husbands, 1960 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - School for Scandal, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - School for Wives, 1952-06 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - School for Wives, 1968-12 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - The School of Princesses, Undated (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Scruples, 1926-10 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - A Seat in the Park, 1926-01 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - The Second Man, 1931 (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Second Shepherd's Play, 1925-1948 (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - See Naples and Die, 1933-12 (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - Seven Keys to Baldpate, 1921 (Box 59, Folder 17)
    - Sganarelle, 1975 (Box 59, Folder 30)
    - Shadow and Substance, 1958-03 (Box 59, Folder 18)
    - The Shadow of the Glen, 1917-1926 (Box 59, Folder 19)
    - Shall We Join the Ladies?, 1927-1928 (Box 59, Folder 20)
    - Shall We Join the Ladies?, 1946 (Box 59, Folder 21)
    - Sharp Practices, 1926-04-1926-05 (Box 59, Folder 22)
    - She Stoops to Conquer, 1936 (Box 59, Folder 23)
    - Shelley, 1969-1970 (Box 59, Folder 24)
    - The Silver Cord, 1933-1934 (Box 59, Folder 25)
    - Simon Simon, 1928 (Box 59, Folder 26)
    - Sir David Wears a Crown, 1923-05 (Box 59, Folder 27)
    - Six Characters in Search of an Author, 1930-1955 (Box 59, Folder 28)
    - Six Intellectuals in Search of Reality, 1934 (Box 59, Folder 29)
    - Skin of Our Teeth, 1945-1955 (Box 59, Folder 31)
    - The Sleeping Beauty, 1926-1929 (Box 59, Folder 32)
    - Slope of a Hill, 1940 (Box 59, Folder 33)
    - Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs, 1927 (Box 59, Folder 34)
    - So Long, 1954 (Box 59, Folder 35)
    - So That's That, 1926 (Box 59, Folder 36)
    - Solemn Pride, Undated (Box 59, Folder 37)
    - Some Women Were Talking, Undated (Box 59, Folder 38)
    - Soul of a Professor, 1922-1931 (Box 59, Folder 39)
    - Sparkin', 1935-1936 (Box 59, Folder 40)
    - Sparkin', 1945 (Box 59, Folder 41)
    - Speaking to Father, 1926 (Box 59, Folder 42)
    - Spoon River Anthology, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 43)
    - Spring, 1931-1938 (Box 59, Folder 44)
    - Springtime for Henry, 1943-1944 (Box 59, Folder 45)
    - The Squared Triangle, 1945 (Box 59, Folder 46)
    - Squaring the Circle, 1935 (Box 59, Folder 47)
    - St. Joan of the Stockyards, 1966 (Box 59, Folder 48)
    - Staircase, 1974-1975 (Box 59, Folder 49)
    - Star-Wagon, Undated (Box 59, Folder 50)
    - Station YYYY, Undated (Box 59, Folder 51)
    - The Storm, 1924-10 (Box 59, Folder 52)
    - Storm Weather, 1972-1973 (Box 59, Folder 53)
    - A Streetcar Named Desire, 1974-1975 (Box 59, Folder 54)
    - Strife, Undated (Box 59, Folder 55)
    - Such Things Only Happen in Books, 1945-01 (Box 59, Folder 56)
    - Summer and Smoke, 1951 (Box 59, Folder 57)
    - Sunday Costs 5 Pesas, 1944-10 (Box 59, Folder 58)
    - A Sunny Morning, 1924-1930 (Box 59, Folder 59)
    - Suppressed Desires, 1928 (Box 59, Folder 60)
    - The Sweeps of the Ninety-Eight, 1920 (Box 59, Folder 61)
    - Workhouse Ward, 1925-10 (Box 59, Folder 62)
    - The Would-be Gentleman, 1930 (Box 59, Folder 63)
    - The Would-be Invalid, 1956-05 (Box 59, Folder 64)
    - Wrong Numbers, 1926 (Box 59, Folder 65)
    - X=O, 1926-01 (Box 59, Folder 66)
    - Yankee Land, 1946 (Box 59, Folder 67)
    - Yankee Makes a Bargain, 1939 (Box 59, Folder 68)
    - Yeah Variety, Undated (Box 59, Folder 69)
    - The Yellow Jacket, 1919-04 (Box 59, Folder 70)
      Includes prorgam
    - Yerma, 1972-1973 (Box 59, Folder 71)
    - You Never Can Tell, 1952-10 (Box 59, Folder 72)
    - You Touched Me!, 1948-10 (Box 59, Folder 73)
    - You Were So Nice When You Were Young, 1974-1975 (Box 59, Folder 74)